University of Connecticut 1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VII:, 1989
  - State Government (Blue Files)
    - Auditors
      - Health Center - Physicians (Box 45:, Folder 2125)
      - Indirect Costs Recoveries (Box 45:, Folder 2126)
      - Law School - Student Bar Association Activity Fund (Box 45:, Folder 2127)
      - Student Organization Fund (Fiscal Year 1987) (Box 45:, Folder 2128)
      - Uncas on Thames (Box 45:, Folder 2129)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (Fiscal Year 1987) (Box 45:, Folder 2130)
      - Vehicle Loss - Undersea Program (Box 45:, Folder 2131)
      - Waterbury - ASG Accounting (Box 45:, Folder 2132)
    - Commission on Connecticut's Future (Box 45:, Folder 2133)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 45:, Folder 2134)
    - Common Core of Learning (Box 45:, Folder 2135)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 45:, Folder 2136)
    - Connecticut Innovation Board (Box 45:, Folder 2137)
    - Controller (Box 45:, Folder 2138)
    - DHE
      - December (Box 45:, Folder 2139)
      - November (Box 45:, Folder 2140)
      - October (Box 45:, Folder 2141)
      - September (Box 45:, Folder 2142-2143)
      - August (Box 45:, Folder 2144)
      - July (Box 45:, Folder 2145)
      - June (Box 45:, Folder 2146-2147)
      - May (Box 45:, Folder 2148)
      - April (Box 45:, Folder 2149)
      - March (Box 45:, Folder 2150)
      - February (Box 45:, Folder 2151)
      - January (Box 45:, Folder 2152-2153)
      - Community Service (Box 45:, Folder 2154)
      - Enrollment Reports (Box 45:, Folder 2155)
      - Formula Budgeting (Box 45:, Folder 2156)
      - Foundation Guidelines (Box 45:, Folder 2157)
      - Handicap Access (Box 45:, Folder 2158)
      - High Technology Grants (Box 45:, Folder 2159)
      - Intolerance Policy (Box 45:, Folder 2160)
      - Manchester Community College Transfer Articulation (Box 45:, Folder 2161)
      - Minority Enrollment and Incentive (Box 45:, Folder 2162)
      - Off - Campus Offerings (Box 45:, Folder 2163)
      - Racial Diversity (Box 45:, Folder 2164)
      - Strategic Plan (Box 45:, Folder 2165)
      - Strategic Plan for Persons with Disabilities (Box 45:, Folder 2166)
      - Technical Education Coordinating Council (Box 45:, Folder 2167)
      - Transfer Articulation (Box 45:, Folder 2168)
      - Waterbury (Box 45:, Folder 2169-2170)
    - Eastern Connecticut State University (Box 45:, Folder 2171)
    - Economic Department (Box 45:, Folder 2172)
    - Education (Box 45:, Folder 2173)
    - Environmental Protection: Earth Day (Box 45:, Folder 2174)
    - Ethics Commission (Box 45:, Folder 2175)
    - Flexibility Legislation (Box 45:, Folder 2176)
    - Freedom of Information (Box 46:, Folder 2177)
    - Governor (Box 46:, Folder 2178-2179)
    - Governor's Conference (January) (Box 46:, Folder 2180)
    - Health Department (Box 46:, Folder 2181)
    - Historical Commission (Box 46:, Folder 2182)
    - Judicial Department (Box 46:, Folder 2183)
    - Labor Department (Box 46:, Folder 2184)
    - Legislative Inquiries (Box 46:, Folder 2185-2187)
    - Legislative Intern Program (Box 46:, Folder 2188)
    - Naugatuck Valley Region for Higher Education Center (Box 46:, Folder 2189)
    - Personnel (Box 46:, Folder 2190)
    - Policy and Management (Box 46:, Folder 2191-2192)
    - Program Review and Investigation Committee (Box 46:, Folder 2193)
    - Public Works (Box 46:, Folder 2194)
    - Technical College (Box 46:, Folder 2195)
    - Transportation (Box 46:, Folder 2196)
    - Treasurer (Box 46:, Folder 2197)
    - Veterans' Affairs (Box 46:, Folder 2198)
  - Federal Government (Green Files)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 46:, Folder 2199)
    - Congressional Correspondence
      - B (Box 46:, Folder 2200)
      - C (Box 46:, Folder 2201)
      - D (Box 46:, Folder 2202)
      - Dodd (Box 46:, Folder 2203)
      - F (Box 46:, Folder 2204)
      - G (Box 46:, Folder 2205)
      - Gejdenson (Box 46:, Folder 2206)
      - H (Box 46:, Folder 2207)
      - I (Box 46:, Folder 2208)
      - J (Box 46:, Folder 2209)
      - Johnson (Box 46:, Folder 2210)
      - K (Box 46:, Folder 2211)
      - Kennelly (Box 46:, Folder 2212)
      - L (Box 46:, Folder 2213)
      - Lieberman (Box 46:, Folder 2214)
      - M (Box 46:, Folder 2215)
      - Morrison (Box 46:, Folder 2216)
      - R (Box 46:, Folder 2217)
      - Rowland (Box 46:, Folder 2218)
      - S (Box 46:, Folder 2219)
      - Shays (Box 46:, Folder 2220)
      - Weicker (Box 46:, Folder 2221)
    - Constitutional Bicentennial (Box 46:, Folder 2222)
    - Education Department (Box 46:, Folder 2223)
    - Handicapped Access, Section 504 (Box 46:, Folder 2224)
    - Health and Human Services (Box 46:, Folder 2225)
    - Labor Department, OFCCP (Box 46:, Folder 2226)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 46:, Folder 2227)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 46:, Folder 2228)
    - National Youth Service Legislation (Box 46:, Folder 2229)
    - Reauthorization Act (Box 46:, Folder 2230)
  - Organizations (Black Files)
    - American Festival Theatre (Box 46:, Folder 2231-2232)
    - Bridgeport, University of (Box 46:, Folder 2233)
    - Connecticut Public Broadcasting, Inc. (Box 46:, Folder 2234)
    - Food Science and Technology Institute of New England (Box 46:, Folder 2235)
    - Peterson's Guide (Box 46:, Folder 2236)
    - Questionnaires (Box 46:, Folder 2237)
    - Science Park, New Haven (Box 46:, Folder 2238)
    - Tolland Foundation (Box 46:, Folder 2239)
    - United Way (Box 46:, Folder 2240-2241)
  - Educational Organizations (Yellow Files)
    - ACE (Box 46:, Folder 2242)
    - American Association of University Women (Box 46:, Folder 2243)
    - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 46:, Folder 2244)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 46:, Folder 2245-2247)
    - International Association of University Presidents (Box 46:, Folder 2248)
    - National Commission for Cooperative Education (Box 46:, Folder 2249)
    - National Council of Educational Opportunity Association (Box 46:, Folder 2250)
    - National University Continuing Education Association (Box 46:, Folder 2251)
    - NASULGC (Box 46:, Folder 2252-2253)
    - NEASC (Box 47:, Folder 2254-2255)
    - NEBHE (Box 47:, Folder 2256-2257)